allegiancetech.com 2013-05-11

# Privacy Policy | Allegiance

## Allegiance, Inc. Privacy Policy

Allegiance, Inc. is committed to building user trust and confidence by promoting and complying with the use of business practices that help protect the privacy of our customers’ and users’ data. Allegiance demonstrates its commitment to your privacy by agreeing to disclose its information, practices, and policies in compliance with Safe Harbor principals defined by the U.S. Department of Commerce with cooperation with the European Commission.

Safe Harbor was initiated to help assure European members that adequate privacy protections are followed, and to identify participating members. Allegiance has cooperated with the US Department of Commerce to meet all principal requirements mandated by their defined policies. For more information about the Safe Harbor program and its benefits visit <http://export.gov/safeharbor/>.

Safe Harbor covers seven principles used to protect personal information. A list of these principals and how Allegiance meets these requirements follow.

## Notice and Choice

**Information Collection & Use**  
Visitors to the Allegiance site may request more information by filling out one or more of our available online forms. Forms on the site include: a contact us form, a schedule a demo form, a request more information form, a partner request form, a pricing request form, or a talk to an expert form. The same information is requested regardless of which form is filled out. The standard information request forms are: First name, Last name, Email, Phone, Company, and Number of Employees. The information collected through these forms is used solely to contact the visitor to resolve any questions and/or comments that they might have.

Companies using Allegiance’s products to collect feedback are given the option to share personal information. Information may include one or more items such as First name, Last name, Address, Phone, and Email. Users providing feedback to a Company using Allegiance’s products can choose to provide their user information or can opt-out and choose to be anonymous. Those products that request user information include a link identifying how Allegiance keeps this identity anonymous. Companies use this information to provide follow-up to their customers and/or employees that post feedback.

Company administrators using Allegiance products must provide a First name, Last name, Email address, and Password to log in to an Allegiance product. This information is kept confidential and is only used to help identify and access Allegiance’s product functionality.

If you have questions, concerns, or complaints contact an Allegiance Privacy Compliance officer:

Phone: 801-617-8000  
Email: [privacycompliance@allegiance.com](mailto:privacycompliance@allegiance.com)  
Mail: Allegiance, Inc., 10235 South Jordan Gateway, 5th Floor, South Jordan, UT 84095, USA

## Onward Transfer

**Information Sharing and Disclosure**  
Onward Transfer Information Sharing and Disclosure Customers that use Allegiance’s products to collect personal information must agree to abide by the same principal guidelines followed by Allegiance. Additional information describing the procedures and policies that Allegiance follows to protect your data can be found in the Allegiance Data Confidentiality Compliance Policy document. Allegiance may at times sell, trade or barter your contact information to business-to-business list brokers in an effort to secure the success of joint promotions through eliminating duplicate contact information. We may append your contact information by purchasing updated address, phone and other field information from national list companies. We do this to help ensure accuracy in our marketing, promotion and sales efforts.

**Children**  
Allegiance, Inc. is a family-friendly company and does not publish information that is not suitable for children or minors. Examples of pornography, offensive language, graphic pictures, or violence are not published on Allegiance, Inc.

**Legal Disclaimer**  
We reserve the right to disclose personal information as required by law and when we believe that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights and/or comply with a judicial proceeding, court order, or legal process served on our Web site.

**Terms**  
No party other than Allegiance, Inc. and participating Customers are allowed to access information stored on our servers. Doing so is a violation of federal and state law. Allegiance, Inc. has taken caution by placing security measures and firewalls on all network servers in an attempt to prevent outside parties from accessing private information. In the event of a breach of security or attempted breach of security, Allegiance, Inc. will press charges to the fullest extent against those parties illegally accessing information on our servers, both civilly and criminally.

## Access and Data Integrity

**Your Account Access**  
Usernames and passwords are stored in our databases. All passwords are encrypted. Account information is kept secure and used solely by you to access your client account, and to facilitate communication. Company administrators have permission to make corrections or changes to their account information as needed. User information is stored only when a user voluntarily gives this information for use by a client company. No information is released outside of the Allegiance, Inc. system.

**Access to Personally Identifiable Information**  
If your personally identifiable information changes, or if you no longer desire our service, you may [correct, update, delete or deactivate it] by emailing our Customer Support at [support@allegiance.com](mailto:support@allegiance.com) or by contacting us by telephone or postal mail at the contact information listed below.

Support Department  
Allegiance, Inc.  
10235 South Jordan Gateway, 5th Floor  
South Jordan, UT 84095  
USA  
1-801-617-8000

## Security

The security of your personal information is important to us. We follow general accepted industry standards to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage is 100% secure. Therefore, while we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security. If you have any questions about security on our Web site, you can send email us at [support@allegiance.com](mailto:support@allegiance.com).

## Enforcement

To ensure compliance, you are encouraged to contact a Privacy Compliancy officer by sending an email to [privacycompliance@allegiance.com](mailto:privacycompliance@allegiance.com). If you do not receive acknowledgement of your inquiry or your inquiry has not been addressed to your satisfaction, you may escalate your feedback to a [Safe Harbor representative](http://www.export.gov/safeharbor/SH_Contact_Us.asp). They will serve as a liaison with us to resolve your concerns.

Allegiance, Inc. appreciates your confidence in us as a web portal and anonymous communication service. In an attempt to ensure your confidentiality and privacy, we have developed controls to keep your information from outside parties. Security encryption of your information using the latest in technology is utilized to help keep your information anonymous and confidential. This privacy policy covers all information collected on allegiance.com, including information collected in Allegiance’s CustomerVoice, EmployeeVoice, PartnerVoice, ActiveSurvey, and MysteryShopper products.

Last Updated on 2/24/2009
